Dixon, Jr., Robert G. Records 5442
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Robert G. Dixon, Jr. Records
1942-1944
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Dixon, Robert G., Jr.
5442
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Decisions, reports, and related documents of the National War Labor Board, dating from 1942 to 1945.
5649080
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 13, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Richard G. Dixon was Professor of Law at Georgetown University.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of decisions, reports, and related documents of the National War Labor Board. Dating from 1942 to 1945, these materials were collected by Professor Richard G. Dixon of the Georgetown University Law School.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Dixon, Robert Galloway, 1920-; United States. National War Labor Board (1918-1919)
5649080
- Decisions of the NWLB, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
- Decisions of the NWLB, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Decisions of the NWLB, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 4-6)
- Decisions of the NWLB, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Decisions of the NWLB, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Decisions of the NWLB, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Decisions of the NWLB, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Decisions of the NWLB, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Decisions of the NWLB, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Decisions of the NWLB, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Decisions of the NWLB, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 14-15)
  Scope and Contents
  Marked for special reference, double and triple checked
- NWLB General Orders, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Reports, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 17-19)
  Folder 1 of 3